

Bringing forth experience developing and managing trend-aware social media accounts on various platforms. Experienced and driven Social Media Marketing Specialist with over five years of experience creating compelling content strategies across multiple media platforms. I have worked to improve the social presence of a small-size business.

#### **Monika Chauhan**

Social Media Marketer & Strategiest

#### **Contact Me**

- monika.thedigibrainy@gmail.com
- (2) +91 87991-99475
- Vadodara, Gujarat
- www.thedigibrainy.com

### Language

- Hindi
- **English**

#### **Skills**

Social Media Marketing & Management

Social Media advertising

Content Management

**Content Creation** 

#### **Work Experience**

## Social Media Marketing Freelancer Freelancing

09/2020 - Present

- Managed all social media pages and create innovative posts to achieve reader satisfaction.
- Worked to ensure social media tactics aligned with the company's overall marketing strategy.
- Content Strategy building
- Content scheduling
- Content Creation (From creating to posting)
- Paid Ad Management (Ad Campaign set up + Ad Management + Ad Analysis)
- Facebook & Instagram Advertising

### **Digital Marketing Executive,**Career Abroad

03/2019 - 09/2020

- Website content & Backend Management
- Managed all social media pages and create innovative posts to achieve reader satisfaction.
- Email Marketing
- Paid ads Campaign setup & Management
- Worked to ensure social media tactics aligned with the company's overall marketing strategy.

#### **Skills**

Content Strategy

**HubSpot Management** 

Facebook Marketing & ads

Instagram Marketing

LinkedIn Marketing

Instagram Marketing

Paid Marketing

Campaign Management

Google Ads

Google Analytics

Microsoft Office

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

WordPress website design & development

#### **Work Experience**

- Content Strategy building
- Content scheduling
- Content Creation (From creating to posting).

## E-commerce trainee cum Digital Marketing Associate,

**Career Abroad** 

11/2018 - 03/2019

- Woo-commerce website management
- Website product management
- Email communication
- Online chat-bot communication

### Digital Marketing Trainee/Intern

#### **Beverage Trade Network**

03/2018 - 11/2018

- Data mining & management
- SEO on-page work
- Email communication
- Lead research
- Engaging with content

#### **Education**

### **Diploma in Digital Marketing**Simplilearn

Online Course | 2017-2018

# Bachelor Degree with Marketing Specialisation,

Maharaja Sayajirao University Vadodara | 2012 May - 2015 May

#### High School,

Kendriya Vidhyalaya

Jhabua | 2011 March - 2012 March